[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "I mean has there ever been a time in American modern political history where the fate of a president has been so determined, some would argue, by straight cash through these strange institutions, the super PAC?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "has", "there", "ever", "been", "a", "time", "in", "American", "modern", "political", "history", "where", "the", "fate", "of", "a", "president", "has", "been", "so", "determined", ",", "some", "would", "argue", ",", "by", "straight", "cash", "through", "these", "strange", "institutions", ",", "the", "super", "PAC", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "In modern times, absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "modern", "times", ",", "absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBG", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Are these misleading, these figures?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "these", "misleading", ",", "these", "figures", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "You know, there's an apples and oranges thing going on.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "an", "apples", "and", "oranges", "thing", "going", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["late 19th century"]}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ":", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WRB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "That's not good for American democracy, if that's what happens?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "good", "for", "American", "democracy", ",", "if", "that", "'s", "what", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "No, it's very much a replay of the gilded age in the late 19th century when we had far few -- less regulation than we do now where plutocrats and people who were, you know, incredibly wealthy, which is fine, they're entitled to be wealthy, represent their own interests in the -- in the polling booth by just, you know, pulling the trigger from afar.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "much", "a", "replay", "of", "the", "gilded", "age", "in", "the", "late", "19th", "century", "when", "we", "had", "far", "few", "--", "less", "regulation", "than", "we", "do", "now", "where", "plutocrats", "and", "people", "who", "were", ",", "you", "know", ",", "incredibly", "wealthy", ",", "which", "is", "fine", ",", "they", "'re", "entitled", "to", "be", "wealthy", ",", "represent", "their", "own", "interests", "in", "the", "--", "in", "the", "polling", "booth", "by", "just", ",", "you", "know", ",", "pulling", "the", "trigger", "from", "afar", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "That's why they call him the POTUS, which means person on top -- what is it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "why", "they", "call", "him", "the", "POTUS", ",", "which", "means", "person", "on", "top", "--", "what", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Jimmy, POTUS stands for president of the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Jimmy", ",", "POTUS", "stands", "for", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I think it's going to back fire.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "back", "fire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "If you're Mitt Romney, what's the smart pick for you?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "smart", "pick", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I really believe in the old cliche do no harm.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "believe", "in", "the", "old", "cliche", "do", "no", "harm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, I think it's true, although she's -- you know, she's in academia and that's certainly a legitimate calling.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "true", ",", "although", "she", "'s", "--", "you", "know", ",", "she", "'s", "in", "academia", "and", "that", "'s", "certainly", "a", "legitimate", "calling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I feel we've had a down period.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "we", "'ve", "had", "a", "down", "period", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "JJR", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "How much should American companies like Apple be following the Starbucks lead and bringing jobs back to America, opening factories here, even if it costs them more money to do that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "should", "American", "companies", "like", "Apple", "be", "following", "the", "Starbucks", "lead", "and", "bringing", "jobs", "back", "to", "America", ",", "opening", "factories", "here", ",", "even", "if", "it", "costs", "them", "more", "money", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Well, I don't think you can have a one-size-fits-all policy, but I do think it's something that corporations have to take into consideration more, and it's going to require real building, because it also means that corporations have to get in the whole issue -- involved in the issue of education, local communities.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "can", "have", "a", "one-size-fits-all", "policy", ",", "but", "I", "do", "think", "it", "'s", "something", "that", "corporations", "have", "to", "take", "into", "consideration", "more", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "require", "real", "building", ",", "because", "it", "also", "means", "that", "corporations", "have", "to", "get", "in", "the", "whole", "issue", "--", "involved", "in", "the", "issue", "of", "education", ",", "local", "communities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple", "Starbucks"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Come November the 5th, who's going to be sitting pretty as the president?", "question_tokens": ["Come", "November", "the", "5th", ",", "who", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "sitting", "pretty", "as", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "You.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Could it be as simple as gas prices?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "it", "be", "as", "simple", "as", "gas", "prices", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "What did you hope to achieve?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "hope", "to", "achieve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Yes, well, you know, when I walked in, I was kind of overwhelmed, too.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "I", "walked", "in", ",", "I", "was", "kind", "of", "overwhelmed", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last two years", "2010", "today"], "PERCENT": ["9 percent", "44 percent", "53 percent"]}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Do you sense that because of people like you that it's become now a public movement that's unstoppable?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "sense", "that", "because", "of", "people", "like", "you", "that", "it", "'s", "become", "now", "a", "public", "movement", "that", "'s", "unstoppable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "You know, in the last two years we've seen a rise of about 9 percent in support for marriage equality, from 44 percent in 2010, 53 percent today.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "in", "the", "last", "two", "years", "we", "'ve", "seen", "a", "rise", "of", "about", "9", "percent", "in", "support", "for", "marriage", "equality", ",", "from", "44", "percent", "in", "2010", ",", "53", "percent", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "What do you say to people that have that kind of view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "people", "that", "have", "that", "kind", "of", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Yes, so there are certainly a number of things anybody might choose to say to that person but I think first and foremost, it's important for everybody to remember to be respectful and courteous in these kinds of conversations because if you're not, you're going to alienate the people who, you know, we need to be having these conversations with.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "so", "there", "are", "certainly", "a", "number", "of", "things", "anybody", "might", "choose", "to", "say", "to", "that", "person", "but", "I", "think", "first", "and", "foremost", ",", "it", "'s", "important", "for", "everybody", "to", "remember", "to", "be", "respectful", "and", "courteous", "in", "these", "kinds", "of", "conversations", "because", "if", "you", "'re", "not", ",", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "alienate", "the", "people", "who", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "need", "to", "be", "having", "these", "conversations", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "-- and it looks like he's the nominee, he has already been outspoken against gay marriage.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "and", "it", "looks", "like", "he", "'s", "the", "nominee", ",", "he", "has", "already", "been", "outspoken", "against", "gay", "marriage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "How do you feel about having a president that would, at the moment, outlaw your parents?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "having", "a", "president", "that", "would", ",", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "outlaw", "your", "parents", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Well, it's a very full circle moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "full", "circle", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "So you're a smart guy, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "a", "smart", "guy", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I -- I do what I can.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "do", "what", "I", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "People even believe that, don't they?", "question_tokens": ["People", "even", "believe", "that", ",", "do", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "AHLS: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["AHLS", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "How are you dealing with your new celebrity?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "dealing", "with", "your", "new", "celebrity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "You know, I travel a lot and that's -- it's hard.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "travel", "a", "lot", "and", "that", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I thought that she was very like talkative.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "that", "she", "was", "very", "like", "talkative", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Do you remember the day we did that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "the", "day", "we", "did", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Well, this is the weird thing --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "the", "weird", "thing", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Like that picture?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "that", "picture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["May", "2009"]}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "When was it taken?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "it", "taken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "That was taken May the 4th, 2009.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "taken", "May", "the", "4th", ",", "2009", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What are you -- what were you doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "--", "what", "were", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "I was -- well, see I -- now, I didn't even see that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "well", ",", "see", "I", "--", "now", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "even", "see", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "-- you're double that, correct?", "question_tokens": ["--", "you", "'re", "double", "that", ",", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "I'm double that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "double", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "What else would I possibly be doing with you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "would", "I", "possibly", "be", "doing", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "How do you look so amazing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "look", "so", "amazing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Oh, well, you know, I lost my parents really young.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "lost", "my", "parents", "really", "young", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "They've never had a cheeseburger?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'ve", "never", "had", "a", "cheeseburger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "You've got two boys, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "got", "two", "boys", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Two boys, yes, 16 and 17, almost 18.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "boys", ",", "yes", ",", "16", "and", "17", ",", "almost", "18", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "What do they make of your strange memory?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "make", "of", "your", "strange", "memory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Well, they've grown up with it, you know, so they -- and they have very good memories, both of them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'ve", "grown", "up", "with", "it", ",", "you", "know", ",", "so", "they", "--", "and", "they", "have", "very", "good", "memories", ",", "both", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 667, "question": "You know, I can more remember the last Scrabble game we had, you know what I'm saying?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "can", "more", "remember", "the", "last", "Scrabble", "game", "we", "had", ",", "you", "know", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Well, let's just put this to the test, because I --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "just", "put", "this", "to", "the", "test", ",", "because", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Scrabble"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "So if I was to say to you, what did you do on August the 16th, 1977?", "question_tokens": ["So", "if", "I", "was", "to", "say", "to", "you", ",", "what", "did", "you", "do", "on", "August", "the", "16th", ",", "1977", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Oh, OK.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["August", "1977"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Isn't that the -- the truth?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "the", "--", "the", "truth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "No, I mean look --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "mean", "look", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "I wouldn't know what month, what day, nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "know", "what", "month", ",", "what", "day", ",", "nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Does your memory go back that far?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "your", "memory", "go", "back", "that", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 799, "question": "Because it's happened today?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "happened", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 800, "answer": "Because it happened today and --", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "happened", "today", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Very quickly, can you be trained to have anything like this kind of memory?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "quickly", ",", "can", "you", "be", "trained", "to", "have", "anything", "like", "this", "kind", "of", "memory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "You may not be able to have HSAM, but I know that I can bring back people's memories in -- in ways that they never imagined before.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "may", "not", "be", "able", "to", "have", "HSAM", ",", "but", "I", "know", "that", "I", "can", "bring", "back", "people", "'s", "memories", "in", "--", "in", "ways", "that", "they", "never", "imagined", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 839, "question": "Oh, you mean it's over?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "you", "mean", "it", "'s", "over", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 840, "answer": "It's over.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]